Andre Ricardo Santin

Curitiba, Paraná, Brazil

andrechillas@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/andresantin

Summary

Hello. My name is André and I'm a web developer from Curitiba, Brazil. Below is a brief summary of my latest activities:

I currently work as a freelancer for Ticket Sports, leading and developing management systems and dashboards for running events with React (Nextjs), typescript, node and deployed in Azure.

Before that, I worked on the Gympass payments team, using Nextis as a frontend developer, working with several BFF services and implementing new integrations and international payments features.

About React:

Styled components and other css libraries, management states with redux, hooks (useReducer + UseContext), Zustand, etc...

CSS:

Responsive design with flexbox, media queries, sass, less, scss, bulma, bootstrap, tailwind.....

Actually studying Web3 stack - solidity, ethers, hard hat, web3js, blockchain

Experience



Senior Frontend Developer

Ticket Sports Feb 2023 - Present (1 year)

Senior Frontend Developer

Invillia

Mar 2022 - Feb 2023 (1 year)

MJV Assessor Especialista em Tecnologia na MJV Technology & Innovation

MJV Technology & Innovation Jul 2021 - Mar 2022 (9 months)

MJV Consultor de Tecnologia

MJV Technology & Innovation Apr 2020 - Mar 2022 (2 years)

Web Designer

Brutal Web

mmda

Desenvolvedor web

MMDA

Apr 2013 - Aug 2013 (5 months)

Desenvolvimento de sites utilizando o Drupal

Desenvolvedor web

Jan 2013 - Mar 2013 (3 months) Projetos

Sócio / Gerente de Negócios

Amana Tykyra Jan 2011 - Sep 2012 (1 year 9 months) Vendas e projetos

₩ Web Designer

Centro Universitário Internacional UNINTER

Jun 2008 - Dec 2010 (2 years 7 months)

Projetos, criação, montagem de layouts e desenvolvimento de sites utilizando o Drupal

Web Designer

Uniquedb

Jan 2008 - Jun 2008 (6 months)

Desenvolvimento de interfaces e sites

Education

Colégio Adventista do Boqueirão

Graduação

1992 - 2000

ENG

OPET

Produção Multimídia, Web

Skills

Drupal • Custom CMS Development • Advanced CSS • Web design • HTML5 • CSS • PHP • MySQL • JQuery • React.js